unclehenrys.com 2009-04-10

# Uncle Henry's - Classifieds : About Us : Privacy Policy

| Classifieds : About Us : Privacy Policy|    |    |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|   
  
Introduction 

UNCLE HENRY'S respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at UNCLE HENRY'S Web site. 

Part I. Information Collection 

UNCLE HENRY'S collects information through our Web site at several points. When you register we ask for information such as your name, address, phone number, email. Our voluntary Survey collects information for our sales department.

We may also use names and email address which our users divulge about other people, [through our referral program]. UNCLE HENRY'S does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 18 to divulge personal information. 

We collect this information through registration forms and our survey (if you choose to take it). To receive our products and services, registration information is mandatory. By requiring valid registration Information, UNCLE HENRY'S insures to the best of its ability that the UNCLE HENRY'S user community are responsible adults. Other information we request (for example: our survey) is optional. 

We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable UNCLE HENRY'S to know who you are from page request to page request. This insures that information you request or give us goes to you and only you. Our cookies do not have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. For more information on Cookies, see our FAQ's.

Part II. Information Usage. 

The information collected by UNCLE HENRY'S will be used solely by Uncle Henry's for statistical purposes. Users who provide information will receive expiration notices, reminders and requested information from Uncle Henry's.

Registered users may receive additional announcements from us about enhanced areas to our site, new services, and special deals.

The information we collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources.

We do not share data with any third parties. Uncle Henry's will never sell, swap, or disclose the information to a third party other than in statistical form. For example: 50% of our users are female, 68% own their own home, etc. 

We may offer links to other Web sites. Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies. Their standards may differ from ours. 

Our Web site offers forums. Please be advised that information posted in this venue becomes public knowledge. 

Part III. Access to Information 

UNCLE HENRY'S maintains the accuracy of our information by requiring an email activation for all new free accounts. Users may access their own personal information and change any inaccuracies they may find. 

Part IV. Data Storage and Security 

UNCLE HENRY'S protects user information with the following security measures: secure servers, firewalls, SSL encryption and other technology and procedures used to protect consumer privacy. 

If you have any further questions about privacy or security, please contact us by sending an email to: privacy@unclehenrys.com.
